Guide to the Program on Non-Profit Organizations, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Various writings and records [computer files], circa 1980-1999; Accession 2005-A-156
  - Various PONPO writings and records, Circa 1980 - 1999 (Box 1–5)
    - Carnegie two-year narrative and program two-year narrative 8/15/84, 2005-A-156-0072; 1 (Box 2)
    - Carnegie two-year narrative and program two-year narrative 8/15/84 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0073; 1 (Box 2)
    - Narrative Reports, 2005-A-156-0074; 1 (Box 2)
    - Ford fdn. 2.0 Gannett fdn. Gen electric 5-85, 2005-A-156-0075; 1 (Box 2)
    - 2-10.87 \FDN backup, 2005-A-156-0076; 1 (Box 2)
    - agakhan 2.0 Carnegie Corp. CONOCO 5-85, 2005-A-156-0077; 1 (Box 2)
    - Equitable Life Exxon educ. fdn 5/85, 2005-A-156-0078; 1 (Box 2)
    - Fdns: re: knauft project, 2005-A-156-0082; 1 (Box 2)
    - Research reports mail list disk 01 12/86 (pgf), 2005-A-156-0083; 1 (Box 2)
    - Research reports IV, 2005-A-156-0084; 1 (Box 2)
    - Research Reports IV backup, 2005-A-156-0085; 1 (Box 2)
    - Research Reports III articles, etc. backup, 2005-A-156-0086; 1 (Box 2)
    - Seminar brochure (9/84) backup, 2005-A-156-0087; 1 (Box 2)
    - Seminar brochure 9/84, 2005-A-156-0088; 1 (Box 2)
    - Aetna Life & Casualty, Atlantic Richfield, Carnegie Corporation, CBS, Commonwealth Fund, 2005-A-156-0090; 1 (Box 2)
    - Aetna Life and Casualty, Atlantic Richfield, Carnegie Corporation, CBS, Commonwealth fund, 2005-A-156-0091; 1 (Box 2)
    - Ford, Gannett, General Electric, Hearst, Hewlett, General Mills, 2005-A-156-0094; 1 (Box 2)
    - Ford, Gannett, Gen. Elec., Hearst, Hewlett, General Mills BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0095; 1 (Box 2)
    - Hoffman-LaRoache, Kaiser, Levi Strauss, Lilly, MacArthur, JM, 2005-A-156-0096; 1 (Box 2)
    - Hoffman-LaRoche, Kaiser, Levi Strauss, Lilly, McArthur, JM, BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0097; 1 (Box 2)
    - 27-11-84 Albrecht - JAIPress - Dill - Gordon - Squires, 2005-A-156-0103; 1 (Box 2)
    - L. Rankin - transcrip. Rankin.doc, Rankin1.doc, 2005-A-156-0104; 1 (Box 2)
    - Ethno.doc, Ethno2.doc, Ethno3.doc, 2005-A-156-0105; 1 (Box 2)
    - Format.com, 2005-A-156-0106; 1 (Box 2)
    - Mail Merge (Working), 2005-A-156-0107; 1 (Box 2)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0108; 1 (Box 2)
    - JDR 3rd Fellowships 1985 1986, 2005-A-156-0109; 1 (Box 2)
    - Backup JDR 3rd fellowships 1985 + 1986, 2005-A-156-0110; 1 (Box 2)
    - JDR 3rd Fellowships - 1984, 2005-A-156-0111; 1 (Box 2)
    - Backup: JDR 3rd Fellowships - 1984, 2005-A-156-0112; 1 (Box 2)
    - Backup of Fellowships: JDR 3rd 1983 Edited volumes Handbook appt's data, 2005-A-156-0113; 1 (Box 2)
    - DiMaggio: Proposal for a Series of Edited Volumes, 2005-A-156-0114; 1 (Box 2)
    - DiMaggio: Proposal for a Series of Edited Volumes -- BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0115; 1 (Box 2)
    - 1984 Edited Volumes handbook, 2005-A-156-0116; 1 (Box 2)
    - 1984 Backup edited volumes handbook, 2005-A-156-0117; 1 (Box 2)
    - Prog. corresp. 7-83 thru, 2005-A-156-0118; 1 (Box 2)
    - Sandor Corresp. 2.0, 2005-A-156-0119; 1 (Box 2)
    - Simon: Correspondence 1/19/84, 2005-A-156-0120; 1 (Box 2)
    - 1-17-86-12/86 Simon corresp. Backup, 2005-A-156-0121; 1 (Box 2)
    - Simon: Correspondence 8/20/84- BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0122; 1 (Box 2)
    - Simon: Correspondence 8/20/84, 2005-A-156-0123; 1 (Box 2)
    - Simon Corresp. 1-14-86, 2005-A-156-0124; 1 (Box 2)
    - Simon Corresp. backup 5/85-1/14/86, 2005-A-156-0125; 1 (Box 2)
    - Benno.JGS backup Denyang.jpg, 2005-A-156-0126; 1 (Box 2)
    - 2/10/87 JGS Backup, 2005-A-156-0127; 1 (Box 2)
    - Rudney: correspondence 9/21/84-11/19/85, 2005-A-156-0128; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Summary of Proposed Studies 7 pp 7 proposed stud. & Budget 19 pp handbook chap tables 7, 9, 10, & 13, 2005-A-156-0129; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Handbook Chapter 42, 2005-A-156-0130; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Significans of employment and earnings in the philanthropic sector 35pp proposed study of persona and job characteristics 5pp news release 3 pp, 2005-A-156-0131; 1 (Box 3)
    - Gabe Rudney-Murray Weetzman manuscript proposal Handbook High Income Letter newsreel proposed studey, 2005-A-156-0132; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: correspondence 3/7/84-9/21/84, 2005-A-156-0133; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Correspondence 9/21/84-4/19/85 backup, 2005-A-156-0134; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Significance of employment and earnings in the philanthropic sector 35pp proposed study of personal and job characteristics 5pp New release 3pp BACKUPS, 2005-A-156-0135; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: The declining trend in charitable donations by high income families 7pp Backup Insert 2pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0136; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Handbook Chapter 42pp Backup, 2005-A-156-0137; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney backups: Summary of proposed studies 7 pp 7 proposed studies & budget 19 pp handbook chapter tables 7, 9, 10 & 13, 2005-A-156-0138; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Correspondence 3/7/84-9/21/84 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0139; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rizzo Document.WANG format, 2005-A-156-0140; 1 (Box 3)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0141; 1 (Box 3)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0142; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney Grant Requests 10/86, 2005-A-156-0143; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Conceptual Section 25 pages Research Program 5 pages, 2005-A-156-0144; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney correspondence 11/20/85, 2005-A-156-0146; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney Status Report 6 pages Working Paper Cover, 2005-A-156-0147; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney Copeland Disk Two 24 pp. JM 1 p., 2005-A-156-0148; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney Copeland Disk One 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0149; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Highlights 8 pages Impact 3 pages Tables 1 & 3, 2005-A-156-0150; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: 7 Proposed Studies & Budget 19 pages Government Purchases 2 pages Nonprofit Production 12 pages 11 Tables, 2005-A-156-0151; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Committed donations 3 pages Prediciting annual giving 6 pages more than $59 billion 3 pages summary 12 pages archive 1 page 4 tables, 2005-A-156-0153; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Nonprofit activity in the input-output accounts 7 pages draft into for higher education paper 3 pages, 2005-A-156-0154; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Handbook Chapter 35 pages info for inclusion in ISPS annual report 2 pages draft conclusion handbook chapter 2 pages, 2005-A-156-0155; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Charity & Tax Reform 2 pages income-giving 4 pages, 2005-A-156-0156; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney: Research Forum Speech 9pp. declining trend 9pp. YMCA remarks 5pp. VITA 3pp. Agenda 5pp. Insert 2pp. Nonprofit Capital Formation 7pp., 2005-A-156-0158; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel J-R Applicants J-R, 2005-A-156-0159; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel A-I Applicants A-I, 2005-A-156-0160; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel A-I Applicants A-I BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0161; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel J-R Applicants J-R BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0162; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel S-Z Applicants S-Z, 2005-A-156-0163; 1 (Box 3)
    - Personnel S-Z Applicants S-Z BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0164; 1 (Box 3)
    - Advisory Committee, 2005-A-156-0165; 1 (Box 3)
    - Advisory Committee BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0166; 1 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence by other PONPO residents Geiger Nitae 8/1/84, 2005-A-156-0167; 1 (Box 3)
    - Fellowships: JDR3rd edited volumes handbook appointments, 2005-A-156-0168; 1 (Box 3)
    - Prog corresp. 7/83 thru ____ BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0169; 1 (Box 3)
    - 12/84 Position Desc., 2005-A-156-0170; 1 (Box 3)
    - backup 12/84 position desc., 2005-A-156-0171; 1 (Box 3)
    - Polivy: Corp. Jewry Letter, 2005-A-156-0172; 1 (Box 3)
    - Ostravev proposals revson sherman NY fdn A. Diamond, 2005-A-156-0172a; 1 (Box 3)
    - 2/10/87 \PRO BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0173; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rosenberg fdn. Sloan, A.P. fdn. Volkswagen 5/85, 2005-A-156-0174; 1 (Box 3)
    - Strategic management Aetna, Hilton, Mott, Atlantic Richfield, 2005-A-156-0175; 1 (Box 3)
    - Packard proposal (5/85) Hearst Prudential (6/85), 2005-A-156-0176; 1 (Box 3)
    - Krashinsky Proposals: Ford, Wilson, Gund 2.0, 2005-A-156-0177; 1 (Box 3)
    - Wood Proposal 9 pages + Anheier proposal 1.1, 2005-A-156-0178; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney JM+Health props., 2005-A-156-0179; 1 (Box 3)
    - James: Correspondence 3/9/84, 2005-A-156-0180; 1 (Box 3)
    - Stanfield/Auld: Pre-world war philanthropy and black America: The Case of Black Higher Education 3 pages, 2005-A-156-0181; 1 (Box 3)
    - Clayton: Company Identification and Demographics 11pp, 2005-A-156-0182; 1 (Box 3)
    - Levy: A comparison of private and public educational organizations disk two 30 pp, 2005-A-156-0184; 1 (Box 3)
    - Levy: The Private-Public Question in Higher Education cover text 35pp footnotes 9pp, 2005-A-156-0185; 1 (Box 3)
    - Levy: Choosing the Private-Public Mix 36pp Save, 2005-A-156-0186; 1 (Box 3)
    - Brazil Script (Done in WScript) (Levy) 1/83, 2005-A-156-0187; 1 (Box 3)
    - Levy: A Comparison of Private and Public Educational organizations disk one 45pp, 2005-A-156-0188; 1 (Box 3)
    - Auld: New Haven Case Study (Hawley) disk one 45pp, 2005-A-156-0189; 1 (Box 3)
    - Auld: New Haven case study (Hawley) Disk two 4pp. RR#4 5pp, 2005-A-156-0190; 1 (Box 3)
    - Hawley: Working Paper Corporate Philanthropy and Federal Budget Cuts, 2005-A-156-0191; 1 (Box 3)
    - Backup in progress, 2005-A-156-0192; 1 (Box 3)
    - Seminar 1st backup (PCF) 12/86, 2005-A-156-0193; 1 (Box 3)
    - Work in progress 5-85, 2005-A-156-0194; 1 (Box 3)
    - Ponpo backup work in progress DOS, 2005-A-156-0195; 1 (Box 3)
    - Seminar 1985-86 1986-87 (.pub), 2005-A-156-0196; 1 (Box 3)
    - Backup 4yrplus rep + 4yrplus 1.rep (general) 3/87, 2005-A-156-0197; 1 (Box 3)
    - 4yr narat.rep backup, 2005-A-156-0198; 1 (Box 3)
    - 3 year narrative + 3.5 yr narrative 2.0, 2005-A-156-0199; 1 (Box 3)
    - Research Report 2.0, 2005-A-156-0200; 1 (Box 3)
    - Allbooks list, primary (ponpo) bks 1st Papers list publications list 5-85, 2005-A-156-0201; 1 (Box 3)
    - Working Paper List backup all list file 12/86, 2005-A-156-0202; 1 (Box 3)
    - Handbook + Edited Volumes, 2005-A-156-0203; 1 (Box 3)
    - Backup documents thru 5/21/85 old/wopa list paper, 2005-A-156-0204; 1 (Box 3)
    - AULD back-up November, 1986 Myths/Newbook WPBlurbs IBM-PC, 2005-A-156-0205; 1 (Box 3)
    - Ruber backups Knauft 12/86, 2005-A-156-0206; 1 (Box 3)
    - Anheier International Directory BACK-UP Dec. 86 MS-Dos WS, 2005-A-156-0207; 1 (Box 3)
    - Advisory committee 5-85 thru ____, 2005-A-156-0208; 1 (Box 3)
    - Work in Progress March 85 5/85 see 2.0 version, 2005-A-156-0209; 1 (Box 3)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0210; 1 (Box 3)
    - Documents: working paper list papers list thru 5/2/85, 2005-A-156-0211; 1 (Box 3)
    - Publications list Booklists BACKUP thru 5/21/85, 2005-A-156-0212; 1 (Box 3)
    - Publications list Books lists thru 5/21/83, 2005-A-156-0213; 1 (Box 3)
    - Rudney backup 11/86 Summary/non-itemizers WS IBM, 2005-A-156-0214; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: High income giving backup, 2005-A-156-0216; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney correspondence 11/20/85 backups, 2005-A-156-0217; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: Nonprofit employement: trends, projections & characteristics BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0218; 1 (Box 4)
    - TiHepg Rudney backups Status Report 6 pages working paper cover high income giving 7pp summary 20 pp, 2005-A-156-0219; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: nonprofit Employment: trends, projections and characterstics 24 pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0220; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney BACKUPS Copeland disk two 24pp. JM 1 p., 2005-A-156-0222; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney BACKUP Copeland disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0223; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: backups highlights 10 pages YMCA remarks 5 pages Tables 1&3 comment 4 pages measures 3 pages nonprofit capital form 7 pages handbook chapter 32 pages, 2005-A-156-0224; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: backups Nonprofit activity 7 pages employee comp. 4 pates nonproduction receipts 8 pages nonprofit salves 4 pages government purch. 2 pages 8 tables, 2005-A-156-0225; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: Backups Handbook chapter 35 pages draft intro for higher education paper 3 pages infor for inclusion in ISPS annual report 2 pages Draft conclusion handbook, 2005-A-156-0226; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: Backups committed donations 3 pages predicting annual giving 6 pages more than $59 Billion 3 pages summary 12 pages 4 tables archive 1 page, 2005-A-156-0227; 1 (Box 4)
    - Rudney: Backups widely used feldstein 4 pages plan for turnover 3 pages wasted tax subsidy 3 pages Agenda 5 pages research forum speech 9 pages income-giving 4 pages, 2005-A-156-0228; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Back-up 11/86 Baker/Rowe/Caliguri/Diver/Colgate/Wallace/Weinberg/Lowndes/Predis/Clark/Leegman Interview lists, 2005-A-156-0231; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Working Paper mailing list (2.0) Backup, 2005-A-156-0232; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Backups preliminary report for the management project 16 pages, 2005-A-156-0233; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton nonprofit management: A report on current resarch and potential areas for development disk two 12 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0234; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton nonprofit management: a report on current research and potential areas for development backup disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0235; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton working paper disk one 45 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0236; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton working paper disk two 5 pages introduction to managing 5 pages memo 4 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0237; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton backups correspondence 10/22/85, 2005-A-156-0238; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton preliminary report for the management project 16 pp. Summary faceset on management projects 3 pages, 2005-A-156-0239; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton nonprofit management: A report on current research and potential areas for development disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0240; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton nonprofit management: a report on current resarch and potential areas for development disk two 12 pages, 2005-A-156-0241; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton working paper disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0242; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Working paper disk two 45 pages Introduction to Managing 5 pagers Memo 4 pages, 2005-A-156-0243; 1 (Box 4)
    - Middleton Correspondence 10/22/85-, 2005-A-156-0244; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio: Correspondence 7/2/84- BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0245; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio vitae backup 12 pages, 2005-A-156-0246; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio: Correspondence 7/8/85- backup, 2005-A-156-0247; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio & Mohr: Cultural capital, educational attainment, and marital selection journal version disk one 38pp. Backup, 2005-A-156-0248; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio: Structural analysis of organizational fields disk one 45pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0249; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio & Mohr: cultural capital, educational attainment, and marital selection journal version disk two tables 1-6 app. table 1 iden. ref. omit.ref. 16pp. BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0250; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio & Powell: Institutional isomorphism and structural conformity 36 pp. BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0251; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio & Mohr: Cultural capital, educational attainment, and marital selection 42pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0252; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio: Structural analysis of organizational fields disk one 45pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0253; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio: structural analysis of organizational fields disk two 15pp. cover1 cover2 ref1 8pp. ref2 11pp. BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0254; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Creating private alternatives in higher education (working paper) 35 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0255; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Correspondence BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0256; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Creating private alternatives in higher education 35 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0257; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities: Their role in undergraduate education 37 pages BACKUP new version, 2005-A-156-0259; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Table 1.1 two pages Spencer 14 pages BACKUPS pages 65+66, 2005-A-156-0260; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Finance and function 41pp. research agenda 1p. BACKUPS, 2005-A-156-0261; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities: Their Role in Undergraduate education 39 pages BACKUP original version, 2005-A-156-0262; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger Backups National Science founda. Proposal 20 pages proposal 5 pages spencer budget 1 page, 2005-A-156-0263; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Conditions of Univ. Research (article) 45pp. BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0264; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities, 1920-1970 Disk two 40 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0265; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities, 1920-1970 Disk one 45 pages BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0266; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Research universities and American society, 1920 to 1970 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0267; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger Backups ch. 4 disk two 16pp. writings 1 pg. conditions of univ. research tables 1 & 2 2pg vitae 8 pg. table of contents 1pg. budget 1 pg, 2005-A-156-0268; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Creating Private Alternatives in Higher Education (working paper) 35 pages, 2005-A-156-0269; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Conditions of Univ. Research (article) 45pp., 2005-A-156-0270; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Finance and Function 41 pp. Research agenda 1p., 2005-A-156-0271; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger Chapter 4 Disk Two 16 pages Writings 1 page Vitae 5 pages conditions of university researh 2 tables 2 pages table of contents 1 page budget 1 page, 2005-A-156-0272; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities, 1920-1970 Disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0273; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research University, 1920-1970 Disk two 40 pages, 2005-A-156-0274; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Diversity & Voluntary & Budget 13pp., 2005-A-156-0275; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities: Their role in undergraduate education 39 pages original version, 2005-A-156-0276; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Correspondence, 2005-A-156-0277; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger Table 3.4 2 pages Table 3.5 1 page Hierarchy and diversity notes 2 pages Research universities 34 pages, 2005-A-156-0278; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger The Conditions of University Research disk one 45 pages, 2005-A-156-0279; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities: Their role in undergraduate education 37 pages new version, 2005-A-156-0280; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: American Research Universities in the 20th century 9 pp Disk 2, 2005-A-156-0281; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: The Conditions of University Research, Disk two 13pp. ch. 2 Notes 12pp, 2005-A-156-0282; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: The Shaping of the American Research University, 1865-1920 Notes 12pp. ch. 1 + 2 disk two, 2005-A-156-0283; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Hierarchy & Div Notes 2p. 3.3 the Colleg. Syndrome 25 notes 2p, 2005-A-156-0284; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger: Syndrome 2pp Notes H&D 2pp Notes3 7pp, 2005-A-156-0286; 1 (Box 4)
    - Geiger Index/7 pages writings page, 2005-A-156-0287; 1 (Box 4)
    - Anheier International Directory BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0288; 1 (Box 4)
    - Anheier Correspondence 3/17/86 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0289; 1 (Box 4)
    - Anheier International directory mailing list BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0290; 1 (Box 4)
    - Anheier (2.0) International Directory Mailing List, 2005-A-156-0291; 1 (Box 4)
    - Anheier Correspondence 3/17/86, 2005-A-156-0292; 1 (Box 4)
    - Dimaggio tables + references (Dominatron & stratification), 2005-A-156-0293; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio Vitae, 2005-A-156-0294; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Correspondence 7/5/84, 2005-A-156-0295; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio Correspondence Jan. 3, 1984 thru 7/5/84, 2005-A-156-0296; 1 (Box 5)
    - BACKUP DiMaggio Correspondence Jan 3, 1984 thru 7/5/84, 2005-A-156-0297; 1 (Box 5)
    - ISCMORPHISM...DiMaggio/Powell Aug 7 1984, 2005-A-156-0298; 1 (Box 5)
    - 1/30/84 DiMaggio: NEH Report, 2005-A-156-0299; 1 (Box 5)
    - 1/30/84 DiMaggio NEH Report BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0300; 1 (Box 5)
    - Tables to NEH report, 2005-A-156-0301; 1 (Box 5)
    - Backup Tables to NEH report, 2005-A-156-0302; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Personal Corresp. vita thru - 12/31/83, 2005-A-156-0303; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio Corresp&vita BACKUP DISK thru 12/31/83, 2005-A-156-0304; 1 (Box 5)
    - Anheier's Interior BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0305; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio Corresp. 12/86, 2005-A-156-0306; 1 (Box 5)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0307; 1 (Box 5)
    - Backup normal.gly center.doc default. sty closer.doc miller.doc herald.doc schott.doc magat.11 kossek.doc, 2005-A-156-0308; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio Corresp. 5/85-12/86, 2005-A-156-0309; 1 (Box 5)
    - Backup of Edvoi disk III powpo, 2005-A-156-0310; 1 (Box 5)
    - 8/84 DiMaggio Tables + References (Domination + Stratification), 2005-A-156-0311; 1 (Box 5)
    - 2/10/87 PJD Backup, 2005-A-156-0312; 1 (Box 5)
    - .pjd 1986-87 1987, 2005-A-156-0313; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: correspondence 7/8/85, 2005-A-156-0314; 1 (Box 5)
    - Formatted Data Disk-7 DiMaggio (Klein), 2005-A-156-0315; 1 (Box 5)
    - Cultural Capital MS (MOHR+PJD) continuation - notes, refs, + tables backup (Tables 1, 1A+2), 2005-A-156-0316; 1 (Box 5)
    - Paul DiMaggio "Structural analysis of organizational fields (tables)" references, 2005-A-156-0318; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural Analysis of Organizational fields p. 39 9/83, 2005-A-156-0319; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural Analysis of Organizational fields p. 1-39 9/83, 2005-A-156-0320; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural analysis of organizational fields, pgs. 39- Backup copy 9/83, 2005-A-156-0321; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural Analysis of Organizational Fields pgs 1-39 9/83, 2005-A-156-0322; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural analysis of organizational fields disk two 15 pp cover 1 cover 2 ref1 8 pp ref2 11pp, 2005-A-156-0323; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio & Mohr: Cultural Captial, educational attainment, and marital selection journal version disk one 38pp., 2005-A-156-0324; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio & Mohr: Cultural Capital, educational attainment, and marital selection journal version disk two tables 1-6 app. table 1 iden. ref. omitted ref. 16 pp., 2005-A-156-0325; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural Analysis of Organizational Fields disk one 45pp., 2005-A-156-0326; 1 (Box 5)
    - DiMaggio: Structural Analysis of Organizational Fields 9/83 pp 1-39 Backup copy, 2005-A-156-0327; 1 (Box 5)
    - Formatted data disk 13 DiMaggio tables (Klein), 2005-A-156-0328; 1 (Box 5)
    - Paul DiMaggio - Vitae 9pp, 2005-A-156-0329; 1 (Box 5)
    - No Label Information, 2005-A-156-0330; 1 (Box 5)
    - Note to AMA - for John choice of med ins plan (wordstar), 2005-A-156-0331; 1 (Box 5)
    - (In Wordstar) "The Private Sector Enters Japan's...." by John A. Rizzo, 2005-A-156-0332; 1 (Box 5)
    - Materials for Journal - Preface, abstract, purpose & scope AND misc. letters (wordstar), 2005-A-156-0333; 1 (Box 5)
    - Lueball [??] stats, 2005-A-156-0334; 1 (Box 5)
    - (wordstar) What Will Japan Do? by John A. Rizzo Ryuzo Sato, 2005-A-156-0335; 1 (Box 5)
    - Materials Relating to 1st and 2nd books (wordperfect), 2005-A-156-0336; 1 (Box 5)
    - Search.mat mgtlist.dat serchenv.mgt stratmgt.ldn 3, 2005-A-156-0337; 1 (Box 5)
    - Authors.txt (author info sheet for Sato/Rizzo bk), 2005-A-156-0338; 1 (Box 5)
    - Management program (Melissa), 2005-A-156-0339; 1 (Box 5)
    - Hidden Heterogeneity in risk Mortality Paper and Abstract of Self protection and the physician 3 self-ins & Market reusable (in Wordperfect), 2005-A-156-0340; 1 (Box 5)
    - 1985 JDR^3 Fellowships 86, 2005-A-156-0341; 1 (Box 5)
    - RLG Vitae, 2005-A-156-0342; 1 (Box 5)
    - .REP + financial repts .DOC 1987 .LST, 2005-A-156-0343; 1 (Box 5)
    - .REP .DOC 1986-1987 .LST, 2005-A-156-0344; 1 (Box 5)
    - .ess 1986-1987 .jdr 1987-____, 2005-A-156-0345; 1 (Box 5)
    - .pub 1986-87 (tsem) 1987-___, 2005-A-156-0346; 1 (Box 5)
    - Grant log commitment list project budgets, vitae & general proposals, 2005-A-156-0347; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: General correspondence, proposals, etc. fdn & corp relations BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0348; 1 (Box 5)